<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General Skills on The Arboreal Repository</title>
    <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/tags/general-skills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General Skills on The Arboreal Repository</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/tags/general-skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Static ain&#39;t always noise (picoCTF 38)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/static-ain-t-always-noise-picoctf-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/static-ain-t-always-noise-picoctf-38/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: SYREAL&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Can you look at the data in this binary: static? This BASH script might help!&#xA;Process / Notes wget the items file shows static is also an ELF 64-bit LSB pie executable file shows ltdis.sh is a BASH script cat ltdis.sh Shows the bash script checks for the presence of the binary file and runs objdump -Dj .text to disassemble all of the file, then only print out the &amp;ldquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Wrangling (picoCTF 37)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/python-wrangling-picoctf-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/python-wrangling-picoctf-37/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: SYREAL&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Python scripts are invoked kind of like programs in the Terminal&amp;hellip; Can you run this Python script using this password to get the flag?&#xA;Process / Notes Running in the web-shell cat ende.py &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; grabbing some system arguments, probably need to grab the pw.txt and flag.txt.en to fill those out Looks like there are specific options for each of our arguments Going to check those with the -h flag after I cat the other two Password is a long mess - looks like hex Flag is really a long encoded mess - glad we have the program Ran python ende.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave a Flag (picoCTF 35)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/wave-a-flag-picoctf-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/wave-a-flag-picoctf-35/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: SYREAL&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Can you invoke help flags for a tool or binary? This program has extraordinarily helpful information&amp;hellip;&#xA;Process / Notes wget the file cat is gibberish file says its a ELF 64-bit pie executable Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a command line program? man warm No man page for the warm program we just got the hex dump had the flag, but it looks like you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to run it with the &amp;lsquo;-h&amp;rsquo; flag .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tab, Tab, Attack (picoCTF 34)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/tab-tab-attack-picoctf-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/tab-tab-attack-picoctf-34/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: SYREAL&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Using tab-complete in the Terminal will add years to your life, esp. when dealing with long rambling directory structures and filenames: Addadshashanamu.zip&#xA;Process / Notes wget the zip unzip - definitely long file names tree - only one file path but with long file names Going to use find -name on the final file name then cd to the last directory to save even more time!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magikarp Ground Mission (picoCTF 32)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/magikarp-ground-mission-picoctf-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/magikarp-ground-mission-picoctf-32/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: SYREAL&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Do you know how to move between directories and read files in the shell?&#xA;Process / Notes Start the challenge instance ssh into the container ls to open the session There&amp;rsquo;s a text file with the beginning of the flag + directions to part 2 of 3 ls -la to check for anything hidden &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; nothing there cat the first part &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; we have the first part of the flag cat the instructions &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; tells us to go to the root directory &amp;lsquo;/&amp;rsquo; In the root, we have part 2 of 3 of the instructions and the second part of the flag cat the instructions &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; tells us to go to the home directory &amp;lsquo;~&amp;rsquo; cd ~ We have the last part of the flag The flag is assembled!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>convertme.py (picoCTF 31)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/convertme-py-picoctf-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/convertme-py-picoctf-31/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Run the Python script and convert the given number from decimal to binary to get the flag&#xA;Process / Notes wget the file Based on the script, it looks like you just need to convert the decimal number into binary to get the flag 56 in decimal = 32 + 16 + 8 + 0 + 0 + 0 = 111000 Entered the binary number and the flag was returned 4 minutes 41 seconds to complete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fixme1.py (picoCTF 30)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/fixme1-py-picoctf-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/fixme1-py-picoctf-30/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Fix the syntax error in the Python script to print the flag&#xA;Process / Notes wget the Python script appears to be the same = vs == as before? No it was correct this time Running the script said there was an indentation error - the print statement was indented when it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been Fixing it and running again returned the flag 3 minutes 20 seconds to complete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fixme2.py (picoCTF 29)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/fixme2-py-picoctf-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/fixme2-py-picoctf-29/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Fix the syntax error in the Python script to print the flag&#xA;Process / Notes wget the script flag encoded in hex, could decode manually but there should be another way In the flag decoding function, the key is set to &amp;rsquo;enkidu&amp;rsquo; - but up avoce new_key it is ste to key, but key is never defined Going to try to set key = &#39;enkidu&#39; below import and above the def str_xor() Realized that wasn&amp;rsquo;t necessary - tried running it in the wb-shell, and the error pointed me to the fact that the flag was flag = (flag_enc, &#39;enkidu&#39;) rather than == like it should have been Making the change and running it The flag is revealed 12 minutes 30 seconds to complete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glitch Cat (picoCTF 28)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/glitch-cat-picoctf-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/glitch-cat-picoctf-28/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Our flag printing services has started glitching!&#xA;Process / Notes nc into the challenge instance Most of the flag was presented Flag will be this decrypted echo &#39;0x62 0x64 0x61 0x36 0x38 0x66 0x37 0x35&#39; | xxd -rp Returns &amp;lsquo;bda68f75&amp;rsquo; Add that to the end of the presented flag and the full thing is revealed! 6 minutes 34 seconds to complete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PW Crack 1 (picoCTF 26)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/pw-crack-1-picoctf-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/pw-crack-1-picoctf-26/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Can you crack the password to get the flag?&#xA;Process / Notes wget the encrypted flag and the checker program cat on both - the flag is encrypted if( user_pw = &amp;quot;691d&amp;quot; ): then provide the flag Input the password, 691d The flag has been revealed! 4 minutes 54 seconds to complete&#xA;Hints To view the file in the web shell, do $ nano level1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PW Crack 2 (picoCTF 25)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/pw-crack-2-picoctf-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/pw-crack-2-picoctf-25/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Can you crack the password to get the flag? Download the password checker here and you&amp;rsquo;ll need the encrypted flag in the same directory too.&#xA;Process / Notes wget the password checker and encrypted flag cat both In the decoder program it looks like if the password id 4 specific Unicode characters, you&amp;rsquo;ll pass and be able to decode the flag The characters are 0x33 0x39 0x63 0x65 Or is this hex?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Find (picoCTF 21)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/first-find-picoctf-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/first-find-picoctf-21/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Unzip this archive and find the file names &amp;lsquo;uber-secret.txt&amp;rsquo;&#xA;Process / Notes wget and unzip Saw the file briefly in the unzip Tried to grep it, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t successful even with a recursive grep Sounds like the find command is the way to go find &#39;uber-secret.txt&#39; Wait! I need to add the -name option &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; find -name &#39;uber-secret.txt&#39; Got the file path to the file cat &amp;lt;file/path/uber-secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Zip (picoCTF 20)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/big-zip-picoctf-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/big-zip-picoctf-20/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: LT &amp;lsquo;SYREAL&amp;rsquo; JONES&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Unzip this archive and find the flag&#xA;Process / Notes wget and unzip TONS of folders and sub-folders - a big zip indeed Looks like a recursive grep is the solution! grep -r &#39;pico&#39; Returned a long, very buried file, a brief message, and the flag 3 minutes 27 seconds to complete&#xA;Hints Can grep be instructed to look at every file in the directory and its subdirectories?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>repetitions (picoCTF 19)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/repetitions-picoctf19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/repetitions-picoctf19/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: THEONESTE BYAGUTANGAZA&#xA;Category: General Skills&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Can you make sense of this file?&#xA;Process / Notes wget the file file enc_flag - ASCII text strings enc_flag - almost looks like an ssh key One of the tags is &amp;lsquo;base64&amp;rsquo;, pipe this into base64 -d Twice? Let&amp;rsquo;s skip to 4 times 6 Times!!! Got the flag 4 minutes 27 seconds to complete&#xA;Hints Multiple decoding is always good Core Lessons Recognizing base64 text Understanding the need to repeat decoding processes multiple times if it seems appropriate </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>binhexa (picoCTF 18)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/binhexa-picoctf-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/binhexa-picoctf-18/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: NANA ATOMBO-SACKEY&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description How well can you perform basic binary operations?&#xA;Process / Notes nc into the challenge Perform math on binary numbers Binary Number 1 = 10010111 Binary Number 2 = 11100000 Operation = + Add right to left, anything that adds to 2 gets carried over as a 1 to the left &amp;gt; 101110111 Operation = &amp;laquo; on BN1 Shifting everything to the left by 1 &amp;gt; 1011101110 (added a 0 to the end) Operation = &amp;raquo; on BN2 Shift everything to the right by 1 bit &amp;gt; 011100000 was incorrect &amp;gt; 11000 was correct!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Luminarium (pwn.college)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/notes/linux-luminarium-pwn-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/notes/linux-luminarium-pwn-college/</guid>
      <description>Linux Luminarium As agreed, I would not be doing any write-ups for pwn.college because that&amp;rsquo;s against the ground rules for their generously offered free educational material. That being said, I do want to keep record of the core skills I&amp;rsquo;ve gained through each section of their course in such a way that the notes won&amp;rsquo;t take away from the challenges - because it&amp;rsquo;s in the struggling that learning really happens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Machine (picoCTF 17)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/time-machine-picoctf-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/time-machine-picoctf-17/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author:&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description What was I last working on? I remember writing a note to help me remember&amp;hellip;&#xA;Process / Notes wget and unzip the challenge folder - a lot of files got unzipped from a .git directory cat message.txt - &amp;ldquo;This is what I was working on, but I&amp;rsquo;d need to look at my commit history to know why&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Checking the tree inside the .git directory There&amp;rsquo;s a COMMIT_MSG cat COMMIT_MSG revealed the flag!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame Game (picoCTF 15)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/blame-game-picoctf-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/blame-game-picoctf-15/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: Jeffery John&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Someone&amp;rsquo;s commits seem to be preventing the program from working. Who is it?&#xA;Process / Notes wget and unzip the files cat the message.py Looks like a half-done print statement git log to see the log It looks like one author is committing &amp;ldquo;important business work&amp;rdquo; an uncountable amount of times, at the same time git branch -a shows only the master branch is there cat a bunch of things - no clues cat HEAD gave a reference location, trying to cat refs/heads/master Got a git code, seems to point to the ee09 branch git checkout to that branch, seems the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>endianness (picoCTF 13)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/endianness-picoctf-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/endianness-picoctf-13/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: NANA AMA ATOMBO-SACKEY&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Know of little and big endian?&#xA;Process / Notes netcat into the challenge Need to find the little and big endian representations of a word Looks like there&amp;rsquo;s a source file as well - wget that It looks like the program will produce a 5 character word and we&amp;rsquo;ll have to guess the little endian, and the big endian representations of that word in order to receive the flag I know I&amp;rsquo;ve read about endianness before but I can&amp;rsquo;t remember what it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binary Search (picoCTF 9)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/binary-search-picoctf-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/binary-search-picoctf-9/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: Jeffery John&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Want to play a game? As you use more of the shell, you might be interested in how they work! Binary search is a classic algorithm used to quickly find an item in a sorted list. Can you find the flag? You&amp;rsquo;ll have 1000 possibilities and only 10 guesses.&#xA;Cyber security often has a huge amount of data to look through - from logs, vulnerability reports, and forensics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Development (picoCTF 7)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/collaborative-development-picoctf-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/collaborative-development-picoctf-7/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author: Jeffery John&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description My team has been working very hard on new features for our flag printing program! I wonder how they&amp;rsquo;ll work together?&#xA;Process / Notes wget the zip Another git-based challenge There&amp;rsquo;s a python file (.py) cat on the commitedit message says to add part 3 to the program in refs/heads/feature here seem to be 3 parts git log It looks like we&amp;rsquo;re on the version with just the flag printer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commitment Issues (picoCTF 6)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/commitment-issues-picoctf-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/commitment-issues-picoctf-6/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author:&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description I accidentally wrote the flag down. Good thing I deleted it!&#xA;Process / Notes A lot of files in a .git folder got unzipped cat on a message reads &amp;ldquo;TOP SECRET&amp;rdquo; Recursively grepping grep -r &#39;pico&#39; .git/* - a few things pop up, looks like it&amp;rsquo;ll be in the log file with the initial commit Using tree to help navigate around cat into the files doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super SSH (picoCTF 3)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/super-ssh-picoctf-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/ctf/super-ssh-picoctf-3/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Author:&#xA;Difficulty: Easy&#xA;Description Using a secure shell (ssh) is going to be pretty important. Additional details will be available after launching your challenge instance.&#xA;Process / Notes Will need to ssh into this one. ssh -p &amp;rsquo;the port number&amp;rsquo; username@destination enter the password It gave me the flag! 3 minutes 52 seconds to complete&#xA;Hints None used Core Lessons Understanding how to SSH into a specific port with a specific username at a desired target is a core skill.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
