<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Neovim on The Arboreal Repository</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/categories/neovim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Neovim on The Arboreal Repository</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/categories/neovim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Neovim (pt. 2)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/notes/learning-neovim-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/notes/learning-neovim-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>Version Troubles I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with Neo Vim a lot more than I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing about it. It&amp;rsquo;s been 19 days since I first got trapped and despite that short time, I feel quite comfortable using the tool. There is certainly a ton of learning still to go before I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to zoom around and manipulate code at the speed of thought, but progress is progress.&#xA;The version that the Windows Subsystem for Linux installs is v0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo Vim with ThePrimeagen (Neo Vim pt. 3)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/notes/neo-vim-with-theprimeagen-pt-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/notes/neo-vim-with-theprimeagen-pt-3/</guid>
      <description>Neo Vim Lesson Series Looking up all the Vim content on YouTube told the algorithm to send me some more. I stumbled upon a series by the creator ThePrimeagen that details more commands in Vim and Neo Vim. I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to only add here what hasn&amp;rsquo;t been covered already. But if you&amp;rsquo;re interested, here&amp;rsquo;s the link to the full playlist.&#xA;Introduction (#1) This covers a lot of the basics that the Vim :Tutor does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Neovim (pt. 1)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/notes/learning-neovim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/arborealrepository/notes/learning-neovim/</guid>
      <description>Sidestepping the Roadblock&amp;hellip; While attempting to work through Git BASH yesterday to get this site set up, I got Trapped in Vim™, which is apparently a very normal experience for beginners:&#xA;After trying what felt like everything that made sense and caving in to my impatience in the moment, I closed the window and learned how to change the default editor in Git Bash and set it to nano:&#xA;git config --global core.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
