<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding on The Arboreal Repository</title>
    <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/tags/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coding on The Arboreal Repository</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/tags/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rower Hometown Map - pt.1</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/projects/rower-hometown-map-pt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/projects/rower-hometown-map-pt-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction An important part of building a continually successful rowing team - or any team with turnover for that matter - is strategic recruitment. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have high quality people coming in as your previous high quality people leave, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be in a tough spot. Many Division 1 teams in the United States recruit from all across the country and internationally to find the talent that will help their team continue their storied legacy of excellence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Neovim (pt. 1)</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/notes/learning-neovim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/notes/learning-neovim/</guid>
      <description>Sidestepping the Roadblock&amp;hellip; While attempting to work through Git BASH yesterday to get this site set up, I got Trapped in Vim™, which is apparently a very normal experience for beginners:&#xA;After trying what felt like everything that made sense and caving in to my impatience in the moment, I closed the window and learned how to change the default editor in Git Bash and set it to nano:&#xA;git config --global core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL: Zero to Advanced pt. 1</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/notes/sql-zero-to-advanced-pt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/notes/sql-zero-to-advanced-pt-1/</guid>
      <description>materials by Bosscoder Academy, found on LinkedIn&#xA;Format The materials are sorted into 24 &amp;ldquo;days&amp;rdquo; of learning, each with a central theme. My goal is to break them into 3 posts, 8 &amp;ldquo;days&amp;rdquo; each, with a distillation of the already brief material in each section as a review of SQL.&#xA;1. Introduction to SQL and Relational Databases 1.1 Content SELECT -&#xA;INSERT -&#xA;UPDATE -&#xA;DELETE -&#xA;1.2 Practice Questions Question Answer Write a SQL query to insert a new record into the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;The Arboreal Repository&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/2024/07/23/the-arboreal-repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hedeenza.github.io/arborealrepository/2024/07/23/the-arboreal-repository/</guid>
      <description>Recent Realizations I&amp;rsquo;m only 3 months into coding, but I&amp;rsquo;m learning a lot quickly R resume website then linux commands accidentally then SQL then Python out of need blogdown website&#xA;Title Meaning Repository - a safe place to store and retrieve information&#xA;arboreal - like a tree, I&amp;rsquo;m not perfect and am going to make mistakes and not do things perfectly. better to log while I&amp;rsquo;m going through it and not in hind-site.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
